var words = 
[
    {
        "question": "لِإِيلَافِ",
        "answer": "For (the) familiarity",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "rootWordId": 56,
        "tlit": "liīlāfi",
        "frequency": 22,
        "surahnum": 106,
        "ayahnum": 1,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " لِإِيلَافِ قُرَيْشٍ",
        "rootWord": "أ ل ف",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "إِلَٰف",
        "waznEnglish": "familiarising, securing",
        "waznTlit": "ilāf",
        "waznType": "Verbal noun (form IV)",
        "waznFreq": 2,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "إِيلَافِهِمْ",
        "answer": "Their familiarity",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "rootWordId": 56,
        "tlit": "īlāfihim",
        "frequency": 22,
        "surahnum": 106,
        "ayahnum": 2,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " إِيلَافِهِمْ رِحْلَةَ الشِّتَاءِ وَالصَّيْفِ",
        "rootWord": "أ ل ف",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "إِلَٰف",
        "waznEnglish": "familiarising, securing",
        "waznTlit": "ilāf",
        "waznType": "Verbal noun (form IV)",
        "waznFreq": 2,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "The One Who",
        "pcklId": "1436",
        "rootWordId": 59,
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": 1464,
        "surahnum": 106,
        "ayahnum": 4,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " الَّذِي أَطْعَمَهُمْ مِنْ جُوعٍ وَآمَنَهُمْ مِنْ خَوْفٍ",
        "rootWord": "ٱلَّذِى",
        "rootWordType": "nominal",
        "wazn": "ٱلَّذِى",
        "waznEnglish": "who, which, that",
        "waznTlit": "alladhī",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Relative pronoun)",
        "waznFreq": 1464,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآمَنَهُمْ",
        "answer": "and gives them security",
        "pcklId": "556",
        "rootWordId": 75,
        "tlit": "waāmanahum",
        "frequency": 879,
        "surahnum": 106,
        "ayahnum": 4,
        "wordnum": 5,
        "arabicAyah": " الَّذِي أَطْعَمَهُمْ مِنْ جُوعٍ وَآمَنَهُمْ مِنْ خَوْفٍ",
        "rootWord": "أ م ن",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ءَامَنَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to believe",
        "waznTlit": "āmana",
        "waznType": "Verb (form IV)",
        "waznFreq": 537,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَيْتِ",
        "answer": "House",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "rootWordId": 169,
        "tlit": "l-bayti",
        "frequency": 73,
        "surahnum": 106,
        "ayahnum": 3,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " فَلْيَعْبُدُوا رَبَّ هَٰذَا الْبَيْتِ",
        "rootWord": "ب ي ت",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "بَيْت",
        "waznEnglish": "spend (the) night",
        "waznTlit": "bayt",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 65,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "جُوعٍ",
        "answer": "(against) hunger",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "rootWordId": 278,
        "tlit": "jūʿin",
        "frequency": 5,
        "surahnum": 106,
        "ayahnum": 4,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " الَّذِي أَطْعَمَهُمْ مِنْ جُوعٍ وَآمَنَهُمْ مِنْ خَوْفٍ",
        "rootWord": "ج و ع",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "جُوع",
        "waznEnglish": "you will be hungry",
        "waznTlit": "jūʿ",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 4,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "خَوْفٍ",
        "answer": "fear",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "rootWordId": 444,
        "tlit": "khawfin",
        "frequency": 124,
        "surahnum": 106,
        "ayahnum": 4,
        "wordnum": 7,
        "arabicAyah": " الَّذِي أَطْعَمَهُمْ مِنْ جُوعٍ وَآمَنَهُمْ مِنْ خَوْفٍ",
        "rootWord": "خ و ف",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "خَوْف",
        "waznEnglish": "fears",
        "waznTlit": "khawf",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 26,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّ",
        "answer": "(the) Lord",
        "pcklId": "970",
        "rootWordId": 524,
        "tlit": "rabba",
        "frequency": 980,
        "surahnum": 106,
        "ayahnum": 3,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " فَلْيَعْبُدُوا رَبَّ هَٰذَا الْبَيْتِ",
        "rootWord": "ر ب ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "رَبّ",
        "waznEnglish": "the Lord",
        "waznTlit": "rabb",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 975,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "رِحْلَةَ",
        "answer": "(with the) journey",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "rootWordId": 543,
        "tlit": "riḥ'lata",
        "frequency": 4,
        "surahnum": 106,
        "ayahnum": 2,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " إِيلَافِهِمْ رِحْلَةَ الشِّتَاءِ وَالصَّيْفِ",
        "rootWord": "ر ح ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "رِحْلَة",
        "waznEnglish": "their saddlebags",
        "waznTlit": "riḥ'lat",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 1,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "الشِّتَاءِ",
        "answer": "(of) winter",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "rootWordId": 756,
        "tlit": "l-shitāi",
        "frequency": 1,
        "surahnum": 106,
        "ayahnum": 2,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " إِيلَافِهِمْ رِحْلَةَ الشِّتَاءِ وَالصَّيْفِ",
        "rootWord": "ش ت و",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ش ت و",
        "waznEnglish": "(of) winter",
        "waznTlit": "shīn tā wāw",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 1,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالصَّيْفِ",
        "answer": "and summer",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "rootWordId": 877,
        "tlit": "wal-ṣayfi",
        "frequency": 1,
        "surahnum": 106,
        "ayahnum": 2,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " إِيلَافِهِمْ رِحْلَةَ الشِّتَاءِ وَالصَّيْفِ",
        "rootWord": "ص ي ف",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ص ي ف",
        "waznEnglish": "and summer",
        "waznTlit": "ṣād yā fā",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 1,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "أَطْعَمَهُمْ",
        "answer": "feeds them",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "rootWordId": 911,
        "tlit": "aṭʿamahum",
        "frequency": 48,
        "surahnum": 106,
        "ayahnum": 4,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " الَّذِي أَطْعَمَهُمْ مِنْ جُوعٍ وَآمَنَهُمْ مِنْ خَوْفٍ",
        "rootWord": "ط ع م",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أَطْعَمَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to feed",
        "waznTlit": "aṭʿama",
        "waznType": "Verb (form IV)",
        "waznFreq": 13,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "فَلْيَعْبُدُوا",
        "answer": "So let them worship",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "rootWordId": 948,
        "tlit": "falyaʿbudū",
        "frequency": 275,
        "surahnum": 106,
        "ayahnum": 3,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " فَلْيَعْبُدُوا رَبَّ هَٰذَا الْبَيْتِ",
        "rootWord": "ع ب د",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "عَبَدَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to worship",
        "waznTlit": "ʿabada",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 122,
        "hasRootWord": true
    }
]; 
export default words;